Most people don't understand just how
mindblowingly huge other planets in our
solar system actually are. So imagine
you zoom out from Earth. Past Mars,
here's Neptune. It can fit 57 Earths
inside [music] it. Uranus. 63 Earths
could fit inside Uranus. But all of that
is nothing compared to the two largest
planets, Saturn and Jupiter. How many
Earths [music] do you think could fit
inside Saturn? 764.
Jupiter. 1,300 Earths could fit inside
Jupiter. Now for the big one. How many
Earths do you think could fit inside the
sun? 1.3 million. Yeah, the planets in
our solar system are wild. And what's
really crazy is there's an estimated 100
billion planets just in our galaxy
alone. Follow for more.